Guide to the Cornell Statutory Facilities Office records, 1961-1975.
Cornell Statutory Facilities Office records, 1961-1975.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Statutory Facilities Office records, 1961-1975.
32-1-2074
Cornell University. Statutory Facilities Office.
7 cubic ft.
Files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Construction files of New York State colleges on the Cornell campus, including the Veterinary School, College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, School of Industrial and Labor Relations, and the College of Human Ecology. Also, some information concerning budgets, and the Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Construction files of New York State colleges on the Cornell campus, including the Veterinary School, College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, School of Industrial and Labor Relations, and the College of Human Ecology. Also, some information concerning budgets, and the Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Statutory Facilities Office.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Finance.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; New York State College of Human Ecology.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Building plans are restricted to permission of the office of Planning Design and Construction.
CONTAINER LIST
- Caldwell Gun Shed (Box 1)
- Stocking Rehabilitation (Box 1)
- Large Animal Research Building (Box 1)
- Plant Science Elevators (Box 1)
- Poultry Brooder Houses (Box 1)
- Refrigeration - Plant Science Building (Box 1)
- Re-lighting Vet. Library - Special Fund Estimate (Box 1)
- Roberts Hall Elevator (Box 1)
- Roberts Hall Post Office (Box 1)
- State College Water Pressure (Box 1)
- Television Studio (Box 1)
- Sensory Lab - Vet (Box 1)
- School of Education (Box 1)
- School of Nutrition (Box 1)
- Textiles Clothing Lab (Box 1)
- Tower Road - Judd Falls Rd. Sidewalk Parking Area (Box 1)
- Warren Hall (Box 1)
- Veterinary Poultry Disease Building (Box 1)
- Wing Hall (Box 1)
- Virology Nematology (Box 1)
- Poultry Buildings (Box 1)
- Sturtevant Hall - Geneva (Box 1)
- Classrooms (Box 1)
- Plant Science - Physiology Wing (Box 1)
- Mann Hall - Balcony (Box 1)
- Electric Sub-Station - Corner Judd Falls Tower Rd. (Box 1)
- Drill Hall - Re-wiring Re-lighting (Box 1)
- Ornamentals Laboratory Fire (Box 1)
- Poughkeepsie Laboratory Fire (Box 1)
- Forage Evaluation Shed (Box 1)
- Noyes Lodge Fire (Box 1)
- ILR Development (Box 1)
- Large Animal Pest Control Facility - ALS (Box 2)
- Growth Chambers Laboratories - ALS (Box 2)
- Wing Hall Reconstruction (Box 2)
- Freeville - McLean Rd. - Simons (Box 2)
- Stocking Hall - Comstock (Box 2)
- Headhouse Fire - Tower Rd. Greenhouse (Box 2)
- Vet - College Dog Runs (Box 2)
- Veterinary College Autopsy Room (Box 2)
- Greenhouse Development (Box 2)
- Agronomy Building (Box 2)
- Plant Breeding Field House Project #1690 (Box 2)
- Correction of Inadequate Heating - Floriculture Plant Pathology Greenhouses (Box 2)
- Fallout Shelters (Box 2)
- Rehabilitation - Caldwell Field House (Box 2)
- Golden Nematode Farm (Box 2)
- Animal Waste Facility (Box 2)
- Cleaning Emergency Repairs - Mann Library (Box 2)
- Fish Lab (Box 2)
- Entomology - Blauvelt Laboratory Renovation (Box 2)
- Geneva Seed Processing Storage (Box 2)
- Agronomy Field Buildings - Project #1612 (Box 2)
- Stocking Hall Rehabilitation Project (Box 3)
- Blauvelt Lab and Rice Hall Alterations (Box 3)
- Laboratory Animal Facility - Vet (Box 3)
- East Campus - Site Study and Utility Analysis (Box 3)
- Plant Breeding Field Buildings - Project #1690 (Box 3)
- Ives Hall - I.L.R. Library - Project #1870 (Box 3)
- Space Use Study - New Food Science Building (Box 3)
- Multicategorical and Laboratory Animal Research Wing - Project #1901 (Box 3)
- Facility Program for Rice Hall Feed Room - Project #1696 (Box 3)
- Space Use Study - Stocking Hall Riley Robb Hall (Box 3)
- Medium Temperature Water Central Heating System - Project #1693 (Box 3)
- A Proposed Conference Center For Cornell University (Box 3)
- Program Facility for Multicategorical Research Wing - Vet College - Project #1901 (Box 3)
- Facility Program for the Laboratory Animal Facility Vet College - Project #1980 (Box 3)
- Facility Program for the Laboratory Animal Facility Vet College - May 26, 1969 Revision (Box 3)
- Vet Library Air Conditioning System - Project #1985 (Box 3)
- Cornell Fleet Garage (Box 3)
- Animal Science Teaching and Research Farm Project #1610 (Box 3)
- Multicategorical Research Wing - June 1974 - Project #1901 (Box 3)
- General Services Raw Products Building - Geneva (Box 3)
- Master Plan of Utilities (Box 4)
- Roof Deterioration - Vet College (Box 4)
- Animal Science - Large Animal Research Lab, Teaching Research Farm Copy #1 (Box 4)
- Animal Science - Large Animal Research Lab, Teaching Research Farm Copy #2 (Box 4)
- Revisions to Site Water Distribution - Project #3480 (Box 4)
- General Services Building - Project #3473 - Geneva (Box 4)
- Raw Products Building - Project #3471 Geneva (Box 4)
- Telephone Distribution - Tower Rd. (Box 4)
- Animal Science Teaching Research Farm - Project #1610 (Box 4)
- Plant Science Building Renovation - Project #1697 (Box 4)
- Reed Farm (Box 4)
- Barnes Hall Renovation (Box 4)
- Rice Hall Alterations - Project #1696 (Box 4)
- Vet Library Air Conditioning System - Project #1985 (Box 4)
- Research Lab Storage Building - Plant Pathology (Box 4)
- Vet College - Basic Sciences Building (Box 4)
- Snyder Hill Water Main - Project #1986 (Box 4)
- Rehabilitation of Martha Van Rensselaer Hall - Project #1770 (Box 4)
- Plant Science Building - Project #1697 (Box 4)
- Agronomy - Plant Breeding - Conservation Building (Box 4)
- Raw Product Building - Geneva (Box 4)
- Warren Farm Barn - Nutrition Research (Box 4)
- Mitchell Barn - Animal Breeding Research (Box 4)
- Barns Adjacent to Morrison Hall (Box 4)
- Blar Barn - Nutrition Research (Box 4)
- Swine Barn - Nutrition Research (Box 4)
- Capital Construction Plan - State Colleges - 1956-1961 (Box 4)
- Agronomy Field Building - Project #1612 (Box 4)
- Electric Work Rehabilitation - ALS, Riverhead, Suffolk County, NY (Box 4)
- East Campus Chilled Water Plant (Box 4)
- Multi Categorical Research Wing - Vet College - Project #1901 (2 parts) (Box 4)
- Air Conditioning Library Building - Ives Hall - ILR (Box 5)
- Comstock Rehabilitation (Box 5)
- Mastitis Control Laboratory (Box 5)
- New Wing - M.V.R. Hall - Project #1701 (Box 5)
- Addition to Martha Van Rensselaer - Project #1701 (Box 5)
- Leukemia Studies Laboratory (Box 5)
- Food and Nutrition Equipment (Box 5)
- Large animal Pest Control Facility - Project #1688 (Box 5)
- Greenhouse and Growth Chambers - Phase II (Box 5)
- Home Economics Wing (Box 5)
- Home Economics Wing 1966-1967 (Box 5)
- Home Economics Wing Contract (Box 5)
- Livestock Judging Pavilion (Box 5)
- Systematic Facility (Box 5)
- Endowed Budget Discussion (Box 5)
- New Power Station - Geneva - Project #3479 (Box 6)
- Rice Hall Alterations - Project #1696 (Box 6)
- Hedrick Hall - Geneva - Project #1686 (Box 6)
- Raw Products Building - Geneva - Project #1686 (Box 6)
- Vet College - Replace Floors - Large Animal Hospital (Box 6)
- Vet College - Correction of Slab Defections - Project #1977 (Box 6)
- Vet College - Autopsy Room (Box 6)
- Vet College - Cattle Isolation Facility (Box 6)
- Vet College - Structural Repairs - Parapet Waterproofing (Box 6)
- Vet College - Phase III - Slab Defections (Box 6)
- Jordon Hall - Rehabilitation - Geneva (Box 6)
- Heating Plant New Roof (Box 6)
- Vet College - "O" Barn Ventilation Rehabilitation - Project #1987 (Box 6)
- Soils Pottery Building - Geneva - Project #1685 (Box 6)
- General Services Building - Geneva - Project #1691 (Box 6)
- Comstock Stocking Halls (Box 6)
- Caldwell Field Fire (Box 6)
- Master Plan of Utilities (Box 6)
- Site Utilities Study - Ag. Exp. Station - Geneva (Box 6)
- Multicategorical Lab Animal Research Building - Project #1901 (Box 6)
- Agronomy - Plant Breeding, Conservation Building (Box 7)
- SUNY Construction Fund - Program Status Reports (Box 7)
- Barton Hall - Heating (Box 7)
- Radiation Biology Building (Box 7)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Farm - Central Heating Plant - Project #1693 - 2 folders (Box 7)
- Veterinary College Repairs (Box 7)
- Electric Power - Cornell Campus - N.Y.S. Electric Gas Corp. (Box 7)
- Veterinary College - Project #1982 - Work in Finger Barns (Box 7)
- Equine Research Center (Box 7)
- Entomology - Stone - Roberts - East Roberts Complex (Box 7)
- Safety (Box 7)
- Martha Van Rensselaer Hall Additions Alterations (Box 7)
- Home Economics Wing Alterations - Equipment Lists (Box 7)
- Wine Research (Box 7)
- Foundation Seed Potato (Box 7)
- Water Resources Center (Box 7)
- International Agricultural Development (Box 7)
- Fact Book - Sugar Beet Project - Central N.Y. (Box 7)